Wait a minute-- a child?
(Leonard:)You never see this girl.
(Leonard:)You just e-mail
and text and Twitter.
(Leonard:)Now you're considering
having a baby?
(Sheldon:)Amy pointed out
that between the two of us,
(Sheldon:)our genetic material
has the potential
(Sheldon:)of producing the first in a line
(Sheldon:)of intellectually superior,
benign overlords
(Sheldon:)to guide humanity
to a brighter tomorrow.
(Howard:)I'm guessing
that future historians
(Howard:)will condemn us
for not taking
(Howard:)this opportunity
to kill Sheldon.
(Penny:)Okay, I have
a question.
(Sheldon:)Yes, Penny.
(Penny:)You don't even like people
touching you.
(Penny:)How are you going to have sex?
(Sheldon:)Why on Earth would we have sex?
(Penny:)Oh, honey, did your mom
not have the talk with you?
(Penny:)You know, when your
private parts started growing?
(Sheldon:)I'm quite aware of the way
humans usually reproduce,
(Sheldon:)which is messy,
unsanitary,
(Sheldon:)and based on living next
to you for three years,
(Sheldon:)involves loud and unnecessary
appeals to a deity.
(Penny:)Oh, God.
(Sheldon:)Yes, exactly.